[
    {
        "question": "which of the following is invalid identifiers?",
        "optionA": "sum-1",
        "optionB": "sum_1",
        "optionC": "power",
        "optionD": "power_1",
        "answer": "sum-1"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a math function?",
        "optionA": "acos",
        "optionB": "sine",
        "optionC": "cosh",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer": "None of the above"
    },

    {
        "question": "Pick out the compound assignment statement",
        "optionA": "x=x-5",
        "optionB": "x=x/y",
        "optionC": "x-=5",
        "optionD": "x=x+5",
        "answer": "x-=5"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which operator is having the highest precedence?",
        "optionA": "Postfix",
        "optionB": "unary",
        "optionC": "shift",
        "optionD": "quality",
        "answer": "Postfix"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the size of wchar_t in C++",
        "optionA": "2",
        "optionB": "4",
        "optionC": "2 or 4",
        "optionD": "Based on the number of bits in the system",
        "answer": "Based on the number of bits in the system"
    },

    {
        "question": "which of the following is not a set of binary operators?",
        "optionA": "+,-,*",
        "optionB": "++,--,*",
        "optionC": "+,*,/",
        "optionD": "&&,||,!",
        "answer": "&&,||,!"
    },

    {
        "question": "i++ is an example of..",
        "optionA": "Post-increment",
        "optionB": "Pre-increment",
        "optionC": "post-decrement",
        "optionD": "Pre-decrement",
        "answer": "Post-increment"
    },

    {
        "question": "Can we use keywords that cannot be used as an identifier?",
        "optionA": "True",
        "optionB": "False",
        "optionC": "Statement is invalid",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer": "False"
    },

    {
        "question": "Choose the odd one out .",
        "optionA": "auto",
        "optionB": "case",
        "optionC": "unsigned",
        "optionD": "int",
        "answer": "int"
    },

    {
        "question": "______ datatype represents a valueless entity",
        "optionA": "enum",
        "optionB": "union",
        "optionC": "void",
        "optionD": "none of the above",
        "answer": "void"
    },

    {
        "question": "Select the user-defined data types among the following?",
        "optionA": "int",
        "optionB": "float",
        "optionC": "reference",
        "optionD": "enum",
        "answer": "enum"
    },

    {
        "question": "which of the following is not a valid Derived Data TypesDerived Data Types?",
        "optionA": "Reference (int& ref)",
        "optionB": "pointer(int *ptr)",
        "optionC": "Array (int A[])",
        "optionD": "none of the above",
        "answer": "none of the above"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to define the user-defined data types?",
        "optionA": "def",
        "optionB": "union",
        "optionC": "typedef",
        "optionD": "type",
        "answer": "typedef"
    },

    {
        "question": "The correct syntax to declare a variable?",
        "optionA": "int variable_list;",
        "optionB": "variable_list type;",
        "optionC": "type_variable_list",
        "optionD": "none of the above",
        "answer": "int variable_list;"
    },

    {
        "question": "All C++ variables must be identified with unique names. These unique names are called _________.",
        "optionA": "constant",
        "optionB": "identifiers",
        "optionC": "variable",
        "optionD": "At that time",
        "answer": "identifiers"
    }
]